export type Joke = {
  question: string,
  answer: string,
};

export const jokes: Joke[] = [
  {
    question: 'What do you call a fox with a carrot in each ear?',
    answer: 'Anything you want as he can\'t hear you!',
  },
  {
    question: 'What did the grape say when the fox stood on it?',
    answer: 'Nothing, it just let out a little wine!',
  },
  {
    question: 'Did you hear about the veterinarian who learned to talk with foxes?',
    answer: 'She was crazy like a fox.',
  },
  {
    question: 'When does a fox go "moo"?',
    answer: 'When it is learning a new language!',
  },
  {
    question: 'When do you have to dance like a fox?',
    answer: 'When you\'re doing the fox trot!',
  },
  {
    question: 'I\'ve been fox hunting again...',
    answer: 'or "stalking" as my ginger ex-girlfriend calls it',
  },
  {
    question: 'A guy brings a fox home, tells his wife it\'s a pet. She asks, "Where are you going to keep it?" He replies, "In the bedroom." "But what about that horrible nasty smell?", she asks.',
    answer: 'I got used to you, I\'m sure he will too!',
  },
  {
    question: 'Why did the fox cross the road?',
    answer: 'To prove to the possum that it could be done!',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you become the coach of the Chicago Bears?',
    answer: 'Be sly as a Fox.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Can I borrow your cellphone?',
    answer: 'I need to call animal control cause I just saw a fox!',
  },
  {
    question: 'It\'s hunting season',
    answer: 'and a fox like you shouldn\'t be out in the open!',
  },
  {
    question: 'Did you hear about the shapeshifter that met Medusa?',
    answer: 'Now she\'s a stone cold fox.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Girl, if you were a dinosaur,',
    answer: 'you\'d be a Foxasaurus',
  },
  {
    question: 'What does a fox call a bunny?',
    answer: 'Fast Food',
  },
  {
    question: 'What does the Fox say?',
    answer: 'I\'m canceling all your favorite shows!',
  },
  {
    question: 'Dear FOX news',
    answer: 'I have yet to see any news about foxes.\nSincerely, Disappointed viewer',
  },
  {
    question: 'Did you hear about that one blonde fox that got stuck in a trap?',
    answer: 'She chewed off three legs and was still stuck!',
  },
];
